export const QuestionsList = [
    {
      question: " I am standing between #26 & #169, who am I?",
      answer:"Spider-Man",
      options: [
        { label: "Spider-Man", value: "Spider-Man" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " Josh likes my style & Pranksy gave birth to me, who am I?",
      answer:"BAYC #5883",
      options: [
        { label: "BAYC #5883", value: "BAYC #5883" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " On a certain elemental table, my home is 36. Who am I?",
      answer:"Superman Funko #7",
      options: [
        { label: "Superman Funko #7 ", value: "Superman Funko #7 " },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "After 324 days, the end of 4he first hour will bring oblivion. Our utopia created pain5takingly by the Emperor will be gone forever. N0t even I, a bad as2 d3m0n can save it.",
      answer:"ON1 #4502",
      options: [
        { label: "ON1 #4502", value: "ON1 #4502" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "I look like I come from somewhere in Asia, but I'm from somewhere else. To find me, burn some paper and check the temperature.",
      answer:"Wicked Cranium #451",
      options: [
        { label: "Wicked Cranium #451 ", value: "Wicked Cranium #451 " },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Before the change, TSFUF QPFHQT was a pretty good artist. Maybe he would have created a piece for us to collect.",
        answer:"Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
          value:
            "Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "It’s all relative. The one stone. 3141879-4181955.",
      answer:"Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
          value:
            "Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "THey were my theRApist, UNtiL thEy QuIt cuZ they fElL for a MadmaN. I realLy miss them.",
        answer:"Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
          value:
            "Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " Let's not forget the living? A boy, his dog and ___",
      answer:"The plant under the desk",
      options: [
        { label: "The plant under the desk", value: "The plant under the desk" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        " Let's go to Ithaca with Todd Phillips. Oh wait, this isn't that movie. This artwork was created by a guy with a vampire Disney Avatar for his Collection that reminds me of Lemmy Kilmister.",
      answer:"Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
      options: [
        {
          label: "Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
          value: "Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " Touch me, and nothing can touch you... ",
      answer:"Starman from Mario",
      options: [
        { label: "Starman from Mario", value: "Starman from Mario" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " The answer to clue is in this limerick",
      answer:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger. Deadpool statue",
      options: [
        {
          label:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger.Deadpool statue",
          value:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger.Deadpool statue"
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        " I share a name with the man who created many of the guys on the shelves above me. I'm wayyy cuter though. Who am I?",
      answer:"Kirby",
      options: [
        { label: "Kirby", value: "Kirby" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
  ];